

Cyril Moran

MECHANICAL ENGINEER

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A driven engineer with a passion to better our community through engineering innovation. Coupling leadership and technical skills along with professional experience, illustrate all the qualities that will make a significant difference in your company.

EDUCATION

08-2018 – 12-2022

University of Florida, B.S of Mechanical Engineering

- GPA of 3.6
- American Society of Mechanical Engineers member
- Generational Relief in Prosthetics member
- BRASA member

2014 - 2018 Sarasota High School, High School Diploma

- GPA of 4.6
- · Cambridge AICE Diploma recipient

EXPERIENCE

05-2022 – 08-2022

Mechanical Engineering Intern

22 Sun Hydraulics

- Developed over 300-dimensional programs for parts
- Conduct uncertainty and control studies on a gage machine
- Design baskets and fixtures in AutoCAD to maximize volume and versatility
- Developed certified work instructions on how to operate the gage machine safely and efficiently
- Led the research of new automation technologies and catalyzed the transition to these technologies

08-2021 – present

Undergraduate Researcher

University of Florida

- Designing an overnight dialysis system
- Create an electrodialysis (ED) benchmark system in SOLIDWORKS
 - Perform CFD and Electrodialysis analysis in ANSYS on the 5-layer ED membrane for a 60% salt retention rate
- Synthesize a graphene oxide (GO) membrane that permits protein permeability
- Design a scaled 3-stage system that incorporates the GO membrane, ED system, and reverse osmosis membrane to test and troubleshoot

11-2016 – 05-2018

Lead Cashier

Home Depot

- Provide customers with fast, friendly, accurate and safe service while processing transactions efficiently
- Proactively seek product/project knowledge to provide customers with information and identify selling opportunities
- Handle dissatisfied customers and customer complaints with diplomacy and guidance towards positive resolutions
- Convince customers to apply for Home Depot credit cards
 - o One of the top performers in Cashier Department.